{"name":"M21_05_Schleifen","currentQuestionIndex":-1,"questionList":[{"questionText":"```\nfor(int a = 2; a <= 10; a += 3)\n\nSystem.out.print(a+””);\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"2 5 8","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 5","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 5 8 11","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\nint i = 0;\nfor(i = 0 ; i < 5; i++){\t\t\t\n}\t\t\nSystem.out.println(i);\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\n     public static void main(String []args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tbreak;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\t\n     }\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\n\tpublic static void main(String []args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\t\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\n\tpublic static void main(String []args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tif(i % 2 == 0){\n\t\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\t}\n\t}\n}\n```\nA.  Program will print all even numbers between 0 to 10\n\nB.  Program will print all odd numbers between 0 to 10\n\nC.  Program gives a compilation error\n\nD.  None of the above","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"A","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"B","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"C","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"D","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\n\t\tfor(int i = 0 ; i < 10; i++){\t\t\t\n\t\t}\t\t\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(i = 0 ; i < 10; i++){\t\t\t\n\t\t}\t\t\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tbreak;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\t\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(i = 100; i < = 0; i -= 10 ){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \", \");\n\t\t}\t\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"100, 90, 80, 70, 60, 50, 40, 20, 10, 0, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"100, 90, 80, 70, 60, 50, 40, 20, 10, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"90, 80, 70, 60, 50, 40, 20, 10, 0, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tfor(i = 0; i < 3 ; i++){\n\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tif(i % 2 == 0)\n\t\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" Code will print all even numbers between 0 to 10 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" Code will print all odd numbers between 0 to 10 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will not compile ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 5; i++){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print( (char)('a' + i) );\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"No output","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"01234","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"abcde","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(char c = 'a' ; c < 'd'; c++){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(c);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Code will not compile ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" Code will print abc ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 012 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was gibt folgender Code aus?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 65; i < 68 ; i++){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 656667 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"65666768 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 5 ; i++){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i++);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"01234","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"135","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"024","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Was passiert bei folgendem Programm?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 100;\n\t\tfor(; i > 50 ;){\n\t\t\ti -= 10;\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \");\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"100 90 80 70 60","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"100 90 80 70 60 50 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"90 80 70 60 50 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"9080706050 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int a = 0, b = 3; a < 3 && b > 0; a++, b--){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(a + \" \" + b + \", \");\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" 0 3, 1 2, 2 1, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1 2, 1 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1 3, 2 2, 3 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Wird dieser Code compiliert?\n```\npublic class Test{\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(;;){}\n\t}\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Yes","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"No","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 10;\n\t\tfor(; i > 0;)\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \");\n\t\t\ti--;\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 0 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0, j = 3;\n\t\tfor(;i < 3 && j > 0;i++, j--);\n\t\t{\n\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \" + j + \", \");\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0 3, 1 2, 2 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1 2, 2 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0 3, 1 2, 2 1, 3 0, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What will you write inside the for loop to make the code print numbers divisible by 3 between 1 and 10 (both inclusive)?\n```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor( _____________ ){\n\t\t\tif( i % 3 == 0 )\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int i = 0 ; i < 10; i++ ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" int i = 1 ; i <= 10; i++ ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int i = 0 ; i <= 9; i++ ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int j = 1 ; j <= 10; j++ ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\n\tfor(int i = 0 ; i < 3 ; i++)\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i + \" \");\n\t\tSystem.out.println(i + \" \");\n\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0 0 1 1 2 2 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 0 0 1 1 2 2 3 3 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0 1 2 3 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 3; i++){\n\t\t\tfor(int j = 0; j < i; j++){\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \" + j + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"0 0, 0 1, 0 2, 1 0, 1 1, 1 2, 2 0, 2 1, 2 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0 0, 0 1, 0 2, 0 3, 1 0, 1 1, 1 2, 1 3, 2 0, 2 1, 2 2, 2 3, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1 0, 2 0, 2 1 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\touter:\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 3; i++){\n\t\t\tinner:\n\t\t\tfor(int j = 0; j < 3; j++){\n\t\t\t\tif(i == j)\n\t\t\t\t\tbreak outer;\n\t\t\t\t\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \" + j + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"1 0, 2 0, 2 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 0 1, 0 2, 1 0, 1 2, 2 0, 2 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 1 0, 2 0, 2 1, 3 0, 3 1, 3 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\touter:\n\t\tfor(int i = 0; i < 3; i++){\n\t\t\tinner:\n\t\t\tfor(int j = 0; j < 3; j++){\n\t\t\t\tif(i == j)\n\t\t\t\t\tcontinue outer;\t\t\t\t\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \" + j + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" 0 1, 0 2, 1 0, 1 2, 2 0, 2 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"1 0, 2 0, 2 1, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0 2, 0 3, 0 3, 1 0, 1 2, 1 3, 2 0, 2 1, 2 3, 3 0, 3 1, 3 2,3 3, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0;\n\t\twhile(a < 10){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a++);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 1 to 9 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 9 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 1 to 10 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 5;\n\t\twhile(b--){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a++);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 5 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 4 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" Code will print 1 to 5 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0;\n\t\twhile(a < = 10){\n\t\t\ta++;\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0;\n\t\twhile(a < 10){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(++a);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" Compilation error ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code prints 0 to 9 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code prints 0 to 10 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code prints 1 to 10 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 10;\n\t\twhile( a + 2 < b){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t}\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 2 to 8 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 8 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 5;\n\t\twhile( b-- > a++)\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 4 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 5 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 1 to 4 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 1 to 3 ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\t\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 10;\n\t\twhile( --b > a )\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t\ta++;\n\t}\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Program will print 9 to 0 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Program will print 10 to 0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Program will print 10 to 1 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 100;\n\t\twhile(int b = 10){\n\t\t\ta -= 10;\n\t\t\tb += 10;\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print nothing ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print \"100 90…..10\" ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print \"90 80…0\" ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 0;\n\t\twhile(a + 2 < 10){\n\t\t\ta += 2;\n\t\t\tint b = 10;\n\t\t\twhile(b - 2 > 0){\n\t\t\t\tb -= 2;\n\t\t\t}\t\t\t\t\n\t\t}\n\t\tSystem.out.println(a + \" \" + b);\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Code will print \"10 0\" ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print \"10 2\" ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print \"8 0\" ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 10, b = 0;\n\t\twhile( a + 2 < 10 && b - 2 > 0){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 10 to 0 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 10 to 2 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 10;\n\t\twhile(b - 2 > 0){\n\t\t\tb -= 2;\n\t\t\twhile(a + 2 < 10){\n\t\t\t\ta += 2;\n\t\t\t\tif(a == b)\n\t\t\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t\t\t\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(a + \" \" + b + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 8, 4 8, 6 8, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 8, 4 8, 6 8, 2 6, 4 6, 8 6, 2 4, 6 4, 8 4, 4 2, 6 2, 8 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"8 2, 8 4, 8 6, 6 2, 6 4, 6 8, 4 2, 4 6, 4 8, 2 4, 2 6, 2 8, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 3, b = 0;\n\t\twhile( a >= 0 ){\n\t\t\ta -= 1;\n\t\t\twhile(b< =3 ){\n\t\t\t\tb += 1;\n\t\t\t\tif(a < b)\n\t\t\t\t\tbreak;\n\t\t\t\t\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(a + \" \" + b + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 1, 2 2, 1 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 1, 2 2, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 3 1, 3 2, 2 1, 1 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\touter: while(i < 10){\n\t\t\ti+=2;\n\t\t\tint j = 10;\n\t\t\tinner: while(j > 0){\n\t\t\t\tj -=2;\n\t\t\t\tif(i == j)\n\t\t\t\t\tbreak outer;\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(i + \" \" + j + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"2 8, 2 6, 2 4, 4 8, 4 6, 6 8, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"2 8, 2 6, 2 4, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 8 2, 6 2, 4 2, 8 4, 6 4, 8 6, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 4, b = 4;\n\t\twhile(a-- > 0){\n\t\t\twhile(b-- > 0){\n\t\t\t\tif(a == b)\n\t\t\t\t\tcontinue;\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(a + \" \" + b + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" 3 2, 3 1, 3 0, ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"4 3, 4 2, 4 1, 3 4, 3 2, 3 1, 2 4, 2 3, 2 1, 1 4, 1 3, 1 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3 2, 3 1, 3 0, 2 3, 1 3, 1 2, 0 3, 0 2, 0 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint a = 4, b = 4;\n\t\touter: while(a-- > 0){\n\t\t\twhile(b-- > 0){\n\t\t\t\tif(a == b)\n\t\t\t\t\tcontinue outer;\n\t\t\t\tSystem.out.print(a + \" \" + b + \", \");\n\t\t\t}\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":" 3 2, 3 1, 2 3, 2 1, 1 3, 1 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" 3 2, 2 3, 1 3, 1 2, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3 3, 2 2, 1 1, ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" None of the above ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\twhile(1){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Hello\");\t\t\t\n\t\t}\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Hello will be printed once ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Hello will be printed infinite times ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tdo{\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Loop\");\n\t\t}while(i != 0);\t\t\n\t\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" \"Loop\" will be printed once ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" \"Loop\" will be printed infinite times ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"No output ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"```\npublic class Test{\t\n\t\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args){\n\t\tint i = 0;\n\t\tdo{\n\t\t\ti++;\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(i);\n\t\t}while(i < 5)\t\t\n\t\t\n\t}\n\t\n}\n```","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Compilation error ","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 1 to 5 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Code will print 0 to 4 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":" Code will print 1 to 4 ","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Regardless of the boolean condition of the do while loop, there is always at least one iteration of the loop.","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"}],"sessionConfig":{"theme":"Material","readingConfirmationEnabled":false,"showResponseProgress":true,"confidenceSliderEnabled":false,"music":{"enabled":{"lobby":true,"countdownRunning":true,"countdownEnd":true},"shared":{"lobby":false,"countdownRunning":false,"countdownEnd":false},"volumeConfig":{"global":60,"lobby":60,"countdownRunning":60,"countdownEnd":60,"useGlobalVolume":true},"titleConfig":{"lobby":"Song3","countdownRunning":"Song1","countdownEnd":"Song1"}},"nicks":{"memberGroups":[],"maxMembersPerGroup":10,"autoJoinToGroup":false,"selectedNicks":[],"blockIllegalNicks":true}},"state":"Inactive","currentStartTimestamp":-1}